<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayanna Fisher</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ayanna Fisher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Post !</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Python and R for Computational Biology In Computational Biology we briefly learned about Python and how it works alongside the programming language R. R is a great programming language because its functions are formatted so that data can be easily manipulated, analyzed, and visualized. Python has a useful library that imitates many essential features in R called Pandas. Since the two languages are widely used in the fields of statistical analysis, many programmers utilize both for projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>NAME: Ayanna Fisher EID: adf2353 DUE: 04/04/2021

INTRODUCTION For this project I wanted to see if there was a relationship between the condition of roads/infrastructure of each state and their corresponding GDP status for each year. The infrastructure data frame used in this assignment comes from the U.S. Bureau of Transportation Statistics –&amp;gt; https://www.bts.gov/road-condition . It originally had 5 columns, listing the state, international roughness index, class, year, and total miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>NAME: Ayanna Fisher EID: adf2353 DUE: 05/07/2021
Introduction 
This dataset details Google Play Store apps and their corresponding qualities. With 10,841 observations, there are 13 variables, App, Category, Rating, Reviews, Size, Installs, Type, Price, Content Rating, Genres, Last Updated, Current Version, and Android Version. Of the 13 variables, this project will focus on variables Category, Rating, Reviews, Size, and Type. After tidying the dataset and omitting any NA values, there will be a total of 7,088 observations to manipulate in this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
